And we're making Chili Verde. We've got our Chili Verde sitting right there not boiling out of control, it just is cooking, let it be.
OKay, we've got out cabbage, we got our lime on the side here, we got that.
Now, cheese and tortillas.
I like to have cheese, alright, and one thing with cheese don't buy fake fake, imitation, processed, nasty crap, OKay?
Get the good stuff, alright?
This is life and food is delicious.
So, get this, you can grate it.
I like to chop it up into thick slices.
Well, not too thick just thick enough.
Chop that up, it will melt right on top of there.
There, we got that.
Now tortillas.
Let's get some nice tortillas, at least get some flour ones.
You can get some that you can, that aren't cooked.
You just take them, they're already made, and you can cook them yourself.
I like to do that, but today we've just got some regular flour tortillas.
We got ten of them.